Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 1
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 1
- Box: 22, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Boletin para Uniones Obreras, 1965; Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
    Notes: Mayo 1965 (several articles)
  - Item 7: Boletin para Uniones Obreras, 1965; Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
    Notes: Noviembre de 1965 (several articles)
  - Item 8: Boletin para Uniones Obreras, 1965; Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
    Notes: Septiembre 1965 (several articles)
  - Item 9: Boletin, 1965; Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
    Notes: Febrero 1965 (several articles)
  - Item 10: Boletin, 1965; Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
    Notes: Marzo 1965 (several articles)
  - Item 11: Reglamento Num. 1 - Seguridad de Empleo, 1949; Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: The Commonwealth of Puerto Rico - A House of Good Will, 1956; Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
    Author: Luis Munox Marin
  - Item 13: Su Plan de Retiro: Un resumen informativoLey de Retiro, 1951; Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: Apuntes Sobre el Desarrolla del Movimiento Obrero en Puerto Rico, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: Primer Informa Annual: Sistema de Retiroy sus Instrumentalidades, 1952; Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Box: 22, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: An America to Serve the World, 1956; Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
    Author: Luis Munoz Marin
  - Item 2: Apuntes Sobre el Movimiento Obrero en Puerto Rico, 1952; Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Arbitraje (Sintesis), 1950; Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
    Author: Julio Machuca
  - Item 4: Capacitacion Sindical para LideresSindicales de Puerto Rico, 1966; Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Carribean Studies, October 1968: La Encomienda...Antillas Mayores, Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
    Author: University of Puerto Rico (Rio Piedras Campus). Institute of Caribbean Studies
  - Item 6: Constitucion de la Federacion Libre de los Trabajadores de Puerto Rico, 1921; Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
    Author: Puerto Rico
  - Item 7: Constitucion del Estado Libre Asociado de Puerto Rico, 1956; Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
    Author: Federacion Libre de los Trabajadores de Puerto Rico
  - Item 8: El Desarrollo de la Fuerza Obrera Industrial en Puerto Rico, 1958; Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: General Information: Puerto Rico, Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Government Financing of Political Parties in Puerto Rico, 1961; Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
    Author: Henry Wells
  - Item 11: How to Hire Agricultural Workers from Puerto Rico, 1957; Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
    Author: Puerto Rico. Dept. of Labor
  - Item 12: Informacion sobre la Ley de Seguridad de Empleo de 1948, Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Ley de Relaciones del TrabajoRelaciones del Trabajo de Puerto Rico, 1957; Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: Programa de Adiestramiento para NuevosNormas de Trabajo, Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: Un Seguro de vejez y paraLe Ley Federal de Seguridad Social, 1952; Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: Discurso del Hon. Gobernado Roberto Sanchez VilellaWorkers' Union, 1965; Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: El Manuel del Delgado, 20 Preguntas y Respuestas, Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
    Author: Textile Workers Union of America
  - Item 18: Strangers then Neighbors: From Pilgrims to Puerto Ricans, 1961; Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Box: 22, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Forced Labor in Romania, 1949; Publication (Box 22, Folder 11)
    Author: Nicolae Radescu
  - Item 2: Speech to the National Conference of Miners, 1952; Publication (Box 22, Folder 11)
    Author: Gheorghe Gheorghiu-Dej